Terry,I know I haven't worked here very long but would it be possible...
特瑞,我,我知道我在这里干时间并不长
...if I got a $1 00 advance on my salary?
但我在想您是否能考虑预支给我100块薪水
An advance?
预支?
So I can spend Thanksgiving with my family.
这样我才能和家里人共度感恩节
Every year we ski in Vail, and my father pays for my ticket.
每年,我们全家都去韦尔滑雪 通常都是我父亲为我出票钱
But I've started this independent thing...
但是我现在已经开始学习独立
...which is actually why I took this "job. "
恩,这实际上也是我为什么要干这份…“工作”
Rachel,Rachel,sweetheart!
瑞秋,瑞秋,亲爱的
You' re a terrible,terrible waitress.
你是一位非常,非常糟糕的女招待
Really,really awful.
真的,真的糟糕透顶
I hear what you're saying. I'm with you.
好吧,我,我明白你的意思了 我同意您说的
But I'm trying really hard, and I think I'm doing better.
但是我,我一直很努力地在做
I really do.
我想我会做得更好的
-Does anybody need coffee? -Yeah,over here.
-有人需要咖啡吗? -是的,这里
Look at that.
噢,你看!
The One Where Underdog Gets Away
六人行 第1季 第09集 气球飞了
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 荣誉出品 河马根据网络字幕微调制作
Excuse me,sir? Hi. You come in here all the time.
打扰一下,先生. 您是这里的老主顾了
Do you think there's a possibility that you could advance me my tips?
不知道您是否能考虑预支一点小费给我?
Okay,okay. That's fine. Fine. Sorry about that spill before!
算我没说. 我为以前用咖啡泼到您表示歉意
Only 98.50 to go!
还差98块5
Did you know Mom and Dad are going to Puerto Rico for Thanksgiving?
你知道老爸老妈要去波多黎各过感恩节吗?
-What? No,they're not. -Yes,the Blymans invited them.
-不,他们不会 -他们要去.Blymens 邀请了他们
You' re wrong.
你乱讲
-I am not wrong. -You' re wrong.
-我没有乱讲 -你就是在乱讲
No,I just talked to them.
我刚和他们通过电话
I' m calling Mom.
我要打电话给妈妈
-Hey,hey. -Hey!
-嘿,嘿 -嘿
And this from the Cry for Help Department: Are you wearing makeup?
这里是“紧急求助部”,你化了妆吗?
Yes,I am. As of today,I'm officially Joey T ribbiani,actor/model.
是的.从今天起,我的正式身份就是 乔伊.崔比安尼,演员兼模特
That's funny. I was thinking you look more like,Joey T ribbiani,man/woman.
真有趣,因为我正想说: 你看起来更象,乔伊.崔比安尼,男人兼女人
-What were you modeling for? -Posters for the free clinic.
-你给什么当模特? -你知道那些城市免费门诊的招贴画吗?
So you' re gonna be one of those healthy guys?
哇,那你不就成了那些 “健康一族”中的一员了吗?
-The asthma guy's really cute. -Know which one you'll be?
-那个哮喘病人还真可爱 -你知道你为什么代言吗?
No,but I hear Lyme disease is open,so you know....
不知道,但是我听说脑膜炎还少人,所以…
-Good luck,man. I hope you get it. -Thanks.
-祝你好运,老兄.我希望你能染上 -谢谢
You were right. How can they do this? It's Thanksgiving!
好吧,你是对的 他们怎能抛下我们不管? 这可是感恩节
What if I cook dinner at my place? I'll make it just like Mom's.
我在我那儿做顿大餐,怎么样? 我会做得和妈妈的味一样的
Will you make mashed potatoes with the lumps?
你会弄成块的土豆泥给我吃吗?
They're not actually supposed to I'll work on the lumps.
这个,他们真不该把土豆… 我做土豆块
-Joey,you' re going home? -Yeah.
-乔伊,你要回家,是吗? -没错
Chandler,you' re still boycotting all the pilgrim holidays?
钱德,你还在抵制所有清教徒的节日吗?
-Every single one of them. -Phoebe,you'll be with your grandma?
-当然,他们中的任何一个 -菲比,你要和你奶奶一起过?
And her boyfriend.
是的,还有她的男朋友
We're celebrating Thanksgiving in December because he's lunar.
但我们只在12月庆祝, 因为他脑子有点乱
So you're free Thursday then?
那么,你星期四有空了
-Yeah. Oh,can I come? -Yeah.
-是的.噢,我能来吗? -当然
-Rach,are you gonna make it to Vail? -Absolutely. Shoop,shoop,shoop.
-瑞秋,你定下来要去韦尔吗? -没错.“咻,咻,咻!”
-Only $1 02 to go. -I thought it was 98. 50?
-还差102元就可成行 -我记得刚才不还是98块5
Yeah,well,it was,but l I broke a cup,so....
没错,但我又摔了一个杯子
-Well,l' m off to Carol's. -Ooh,ooh,why don't we invite her?
-我到卡萝那里去 -ooh,ooh! 我们干嘛不叫上她?
Ooh,ooh,because she's my ex-wife and will want to bring her...
因为她是我的前妻, 而且她可能还想带上她的
...ooh,ooh,lesbian life partner.
女同志!
Hi. Is Carol here?
卡萝在吗?
-No,she's at a faculty meeting. -I just came by to pick up my skull.
-她开教工会去了 -噢,我过来想把我的头骨拿走
Well,not mine,but....
嗯,不是我的,是…
-Come in. -Thanks.
-进来! -谢谢
Carol borrowed it,and I have to get it back to the museum.
谢谢.是这样,卡萝上回借走上课用的 我现在得拿回去还给博物馆
-What's it look like? -Kind of like a big face without skin.
-它是什么样子? -就象一张没有皮的大脸
Yes. I'm familiar with the concept.
是的,我有点印象
-We can just look for it. -Okay.
-我们来找找看. -好吧
Wow,you guys sure have a lot of books about being a lesbian.
哇,你们有这么多讲怎样成为一名女同志的书
Well,you know, you have to take a course.
嗯,你知道吗,你必须接受一门课程
Otherwise they don't let you do it.
否则,他们不让你当同性恋
Hey,Yertle the Turtle! A classic.
嘿,嘿,《Yertle the Turtle》.经典作品
Actually,I'm reading it to the baby.
没错,我现在在念给宝宝听
The baby that hasn't been born yet?
噢,那个还没出生的宝宝?
Wouldn't that mean you're crazy?
你这不是疯了?
You don't think they can hear sounds in there?
什么,你觉得宝宝在里面听不到声音?
You' re not serious? I mean,you really talk to it?
少来,我的意思是… 真的 你…真的宝宝说话吗?
Yeah,all the time. I want the baby to know my voice.
当然,经常说.我要让宝宝记住我的声音
Well,that's just Do you talk about me?
那,你提到过我吗?
-Yeah. All the time. -Really?
-有的,常事. -真的?
But,we just refer to you as " Bobo the Sperm Guy. "
但是,嗯,我们称你为提供精液的BoBo
If she's talking to it,I just think I should get some belly time too.
不行,如果她和宝宝说话 那我也应该有一些“肚子谈话时间”
Not that I believe this.
但这不表示我相信这个
I believe it. I think the baby can hear everything.
噢,我相信.我觉得宝宝什么都能听见
-Really? -I'll show you. This'll seem weird.
-真的? -我可以演示给你看.可能会有点怪异
But you put your head inside this turkey...
你得把你的头放在这只火鸡里面
...and we'll all talk and you'll hear everything we say.
然后大伙儿说话,你肯定能听到我们说的
I'd just like to say I'm totally behind this experiment.
我想说我完全赞成这个实验
In fact,I'd very much like to butter your head.
而且,我还非常想把你的脑袋涂上黄油
-Hey. -Rach,did you make your money?
-嘿 -瑞秋,钱拿到没有?
No,not even close. Forget Vail. Forget seeing my family.
没有,都关门了 忘掉韦尔吧, 忘掉家庭团聚吧
Forget shoop,shoop,shoop.
忘掉“咻,咻,咻.”吧
-Rach,here's your mail. -Thanks. You can put it on the table.
瑞秋,你的信 -谢谢,放在桌上就行了
No. Here's your mail!
不,这是你的信!
Thanks. You can put it on the table!
谢谢,你把它放在桌子上就行了
Would you just open it!
你不想现在就打开它吗?
Oh,my God! You guys are great!
喔,天哪!你们真好!
We all chipped in.
大伙凑的
-We did? -You owe me $20.
-大伙? -你欠我20块
Thank you. Thank you so much!
谢谢!太感谢了!
Chandler,got your traditional holiday feast. T omato soup...
钱德,这是你的感恩节大餐 你的西红柿汤
...grilled-cheese fixings and a family-size bag of Funyuns.
你的奶酪杂拌和你的特大号洋葱小吃
This is your Thanksgiving dinner? What is it with you and this holiday?
等等,钱德,这是你的感恩节晚餐吗? 你和这个节到底有什么过不去的?
-I'm 9 years old. -I hate this story!
-好吧,我9岁那年… -噢,我厌恶这个故事
We've finished this magnificent Thanksgiving dinner. I have...
我们全家刚刚吃完一顿丰盛的感恩节大餐.我…
...a mouthful of pumpkin pie.
…塞了满嘴的南瓜派
And then my parents tell me they're getting divorced.
我的父母就选择那会来告诉我: 他们要离婚了
Oh,my God!
噢,天!
Very difficult to enjoy Thanksgiving dinner once you've seen it in reverse.
是的.一旦你有过这样的负面印象 就很难对感恩节大餐有兴趣了
What's this? I never saw this at Mom's.
这是什么? 我从没在妈妈的感恩节大餐中看到这个
-It's a yam. -Hello....
-这是红薯 -Hello….
This isn't a yam. Yam comes in purple cans.
这不是红薯.红薯都是放在紫色罐头里的
They don't They don't come in these.
不是的,红薯不是放在这里的
Ross,don't take this the wrong way or anything,but back off.
罗斯,不要用那种错误的方法,过来帮忙
Hi.
Hi
-We used to work together. -We did?
-我们一起工作过 -有吗?
Yeah,at Macy's. You' re the Obsession girl,right?
是的,在Macy百货 你是那个“迷幻”女郎,对吧?
-Yes. -I was the Aramis guy.
-是的 -我是那卖“阿拉米香水”的
-Aramis. Aramis. Aramis. -Yeah,right!
-阿拉米?阿拉米? -哦,想起来了
-You' re the best in the business. -Get out.
-我得说, 你是那里面最棒的 -少来了!
You' re amazing! You know when to spritz. You know when to lay back.
我是说真的.你太让人吃惊了 你的表演是那样张弛有度
Really? You don't know what that means to me.
真的吗? 我受宠若惊了
You smell great tonight. What are you wearing?
你今晚闻起来妙极了. 你身上是什么?
Nothing.
什么也没有!
-Listen,do you wanna go get a drink? -Yeah,that would be
-你想不想去喝上一杯? -好的,哦
-What's wrong? -I have to do something.
-怎么了? -我刚想起,我还有要紧的事要做
What?
噢,什么事情?
-Leave. -Wait,wait,wait!
-离开 -等等,嘿,等等!
“马里奥没有告诉你的事…他有性病 你永远无从知道谁会染上它”（广告词）
So I guess you all saw it.
我想你们都看见了
-What? -Saw what?
-什么? -看见什么?
No,we' re just laughing. You know how laughter can be infectious.
不,我们只是在笑.你知道,笑也是会传染的
Set another place for Thanksgiving. My entire family thinks I have VD.
我得另找个地方过感恩节了 我全家都认为我有花柳病
"T onight,on a very special Blossom. "
今夜,此花怒放
Looking good! Okay!
嗯,看起来不错.Ok
Cider's mulling,turkey's turkeying, yams are yamming....
苹果酒搞定,火鸡搞定,红薯搞定
What?
怎么了?
I don't know. It's just not the same without Mom in the kitchen.
我不知道.妈妈不在厨房感觉就是不一样
Get out and stop annoying me!
够了!出去别烦我!
Oh,that's closer.
oh,有点象了
I got the tickets!
我拿到票了! 我拿到票了!
Five hours from now, shoop,shoop,shoop!
再过5个小时我就要 “咻,咻,咻.”
-Oh,you must stop shooping. -Okay,l' m gonna get my stuff.
-噢,别“咻”了,好吗? -Ok,我去收拾行李
Will you come in?
钱德,你今晚会来吗?
I prefer to keep a safe distance from all this merriment.
不,我喜欢和欢乐保持安全距离!
Look out! Incoming pumpkin pie!
注意,南瓜派来了!
We laughed when you did it with the stuffing,but that's not funny.
你在塞填料的时候我们都有笑, 但是这会不好笑了
Hey,Monica,I got a question. I don't see any T ator T ots.
喂,莫尼卡,我有一个问题 我没看见有塔特酒
-That's not a question. -My mom makes them. It's a tradition.
-这不叫问题! -但是我的妈妈总是做的.好象是个传统
You get a piece of turkey on your fork, a little cranberry sauce and a T ot!
弄点火鸡肉在叉子上, 配上点蓝莓,还有塔特酒!
I mean,it's bad enough I can't be with my family because of my disease.
因为我的“病”,我不能与家人团聚了, 真糟糕透了
All right. Fine.
好吧,好吧
Tonight's potatoes will be mashed, with lumps and in the form of Tots.
今晚的土豆泥会有成块的和有酒味的
All right,I'm off to talk to my unborn child.
我要去和还没出生的宝宝说话了
Okay,Mom never hit.
Ok,妈妈从不打我
Okay,all done.
Ok,搞定了
Phoebe,did you whip the pota? Ross needs lumps!
干吗,菲比,你在搅烂土豆吗?罗斯要吃块状的!
Oh,l' m sorry! I just
噢,很抱歉
I thought we could have them whipped and then add some peas and onions.
噢,我以为搅烂了以后, 可以加一些豌豆和洋葱
Why do that?
为什么我们要那样做?
Because then they'd be just like my mom used to make it,before she died.
嗯,因为我妈都是那样做的, 你知道,在她去世之前
Okay. Three kinds of potatoes coming up.
好吧,第3种吃法出现
Okay. Goodbye,you guys! Thanks for everything!
Ok,大伙,再见. 感谢你们
Oh,God,look at Sorry! I'm so sorry.
Oh,抱歉! 噢,抱歉!
An unbelievable thing happened! Underdog got away!
最不可思议事情发生了! “点头狗”刚刚飞了!
-The balloon? -No,no,the actual cartoon character.
-那个气球吗? -不,是真的卡通人物
Of course the balloon!
当然是那个气球!
He broke free and was spotted flying over Washington Square Park.
Macy百货前他断线了 后来在华盛顿广场公园上又被发现了
-I'm going to the roof. Who's with me? -I can't!
-我要上屋顶去看,谁要去? -我不去了
An 80-foot dog over the city? How often does that happen?
来吧.80英尺长的充气狗在城市上空游荡 机不可失哦?
Almost never.
太难得了
-Got the keys? -Okay.
-拿上钥匙… -ok
Anytime you' re ready.
任何时候只要你准备好了
Okay. Okay,here we go.
好的,好的,开始
Okay. Where am I talking to here?
这里吗,我得对着哪里说?
There is one way that offers a certain acoustical advantage,but....
我的意思是: 好象只有那样才能让他听见,但是 …
Just aim for the bump.
对着鼓出来的地方就可以
Okay.
Okay
Okay. Okay. Okay,here goes.
好的,开始了
You know,I can't do this. This is
你知道,我,你知道,我做不出来
It's too weird. I feel stupid.
噢,这太奇怪了.我感到自己象个傻瓜
It's fine. You don't have to do it just because Susan does it.
那你就别说了 你不必因为苏珊做了你就非得做
Hello,baby. Hello. Hello.
你好吗?宝宝!你好,你好
the moment we first saw the dog shadow fall over the park!
大狗在公园上的时候挺好玩的
But did they have to shoot him down? That was just mean.
是的,但是他们必须把他射下来吗? 真是作孽
Right now the turkey should be crispy on the outside...
现在火鸡应该是外焦…
...and juicy on the inside.
…而且里嫩了
Why are we standing here?
还站在这里干嘛?
We're waiting for you to open the door. You have the keys.
-等你开门.你拿的钥匙 -没有,我没拿
No,I don't.
我没有
Yes,you do. When we left, you said,"Got the keys. "
你拿了.出来的时候,你说拿了钥匙
No,I didn't. I asked,"Got the keys? "
我没有.我说:“拿上钥匙”?
No,no,no. You said,"Got the keys! "
不、不、不.你是说:“拿了钥匙”
Do either of you have the keys?
你们俩都没带?
-The oven is on! -I've gotta get my ticket!
-烤炉还开着 -噢,我得拿我的票!
-Wait! We have a copy of your key. -Get it!
-等等,我们有一把你家的备用钥匙 -快去拿,快去!
That tone won't make me go any faster.
你这种语气无法加快我的速度
-Joey. -That one will.
-乔伊！ -这还凑合
And everyone's telling me, "You gotta pick a major. "
每个人都对我说:你得选个专业
So on a dare,I picked paleontology.
于是我鼓起勇气挑了古生物学
And you have no idea what I'm saying, because,face it,you' re a fetus.
可能你不懂我正说什么 我们得面对现实,你还是一个胎儿
You're happy you don't have gills anymore.
你应该高兴因为你不会再有鳃
You don't have to talk to it. You can sing
你不用老是说话,你也可以对它唱歌
Please. I am not singing to your stomach,okay?
噢.拜托,我才不想对着你的肚子唱歌!
How's it going?
进展如何?
Here we come
嘘! 正忙着呢
Walking down the street
沿着那些街道走着
Get the funniest looks from Everyone we meet
每人人的表情都很可笑
Hey,hey
嘿,嘿!
-Hey,did you just feel that? -I did.
-喂,噢,你觉着到了吗? -是的,我有
-Does it always? -That was the first.
-他总这样吗,噢 ? -不,没有,这是第一次
IKeep singing! IKeep singing!
接着唱!接着唱!
Hey,hey,you 're my baby And I can 't wait to meet you
嘿,嘿,你是我的宝宝,我已经等不及想见你
When you come out I'll buy you a bagel Then we 'll go to the zoo
等你出来后,我会为你买百吉饼 然后带你去动物园
-lt did it again! -I felt it that time!
-又来了一次! -这次我也感觉到了!
Hey,hey,I'm your daddy I'm the one without any breasts
“嘿,嘿,我是你的爸爸.没有乳房的那个…”
This is great. It's 5:00. My plane is pulling away from the gate.
真是太棒了.现在已经五点了 我的飞机已经从登记口拖走了
-Maybe you can take a later flight. -There is none.
-也许你可以搭晚班飞机 -没有了
-You can go tomorrow. -T omorrow is not Thanksgiving!
-你可以明天去 -明天就不是感恩节了!
If l' m gonna cheer you up, you have to meet me halfway.
我想让你开心一点,你却总是中间打断我
Can you go any faster?
你能快一点吗?
I got one keyhole and a zillion keys! You do the math.
锁眼只有一个,而钥匙有上千把 你算算看
Why do you guys have so many keys in there anyway?
你怎么会有那么多钥匙?
For an emergency just like this.
以备不时之需,就象现在这样
All right. Listen,smirky!
你听着,假笑的家伙
If not for your stupid balloon, I'd be on a plane...
要不是你和你那该死的气球, 现在我就在飞机上…
...watching a woman do this... right now. But l' m not!
…对着空中小姐指手画脚了 但现在我却不能!
You said you had the keys!
你说你带了钥匙,我发誓
No,I didn't! I wouldn't say I had the keys unless I had the keys!
不,没有.我如果拿了钥匙,我会说“拿了” 显然我没拿那该死的钥匙
That's it! Enough with the keys. No one say keys!
够了,别再提钥匙了
Why would I have the keys?!
为什么我应该拿钥匙?
-Aside from the fact you said you did? -I didn't!
-不考虑你说你拿了的事实? -但是我没拿
-You should've. -Why?
-嗯,你应该拿 -为什么?
-Because! -Why?
-因为! -为什么?
Everything's my responsibility? Isn't it enough that l' m making dinner?
因为一切事情都该是我的责任吗? 难道我给大家准备感恩节晚餐还不够吗?
Everyone wants a different kind of potato,so I'm making them.
每个人要的土豆泥都不一样 我得做各种样式的土豆泥
Does anybody care what kind of potatoes I want? No!
有谁关心过我要哪种土豆泥吗?
No! No!
没有,没有…
Just as long as Phoebe gets her peas and onions,and Mario gets his T ots
菲比要有洋葱和豌豆的土豆泥 “马里奥”要有塔特酒口味的
It's my first Thanksgiving,and l
这是我第一次搞感恩节大餐
It's all burnt,and I can't....
现在全焦了,…我…
Monica,only dogs can hear you now. Look,the door's open. Here we go.
莫尼卡,只有狗现在能听见你说的 好了,门已经开.进去吧
-All right,Chandler,don't lose this. -No
-好吧,钱德,别把钥匙丢了. -不
Well,the turkey's burnt!
嗯,火鸡烧焦了
Potatoes are ruined! Potatoes are ruined! Potatoes are ruined!
土豆完了,土豆完了,土豆完了
Here we come
“我们沿着…”?
Walking down the
走下去
This doesn't smell like Mom's.
妈妈的厨房可不是这个味
It doesn't,does it? You wanted lumps? Here you go,buddy. You got one!
不象是吧? 你不是要土豆块吗 罗斯? 好,拿去,伙计.这里倒有一个!
-Don't yell at me. You burned dinner! -Hey,don't make her squeak again!
-不要对我吼.是你把晚饭烧着了 -嗨,不要让她再发飙啦!
God,this is great! The plane is gone. I guess I'm stuck here with you guys.
噢,天哪, 飞机已经飞走了 看来我只能留下来和你们呆在一起了
We all had better plans. This was nobody's first choice!
我们本来都有个不错的计划的 这不是大伙的第一个选择
Oh,really? So why was I busting my ass to make this delicious dinner?
噢,真的吗? 那我何苦为什么做这顿丰盛 的感恩节大餐?
-You call that delicious? -You be quiet!
-你管这叫丰盛吗? -给我安静!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
闭嘴,闭嘴,闭嘴!
Now this feels like Thanksgiving.
终于有了点感恩节的气氛了
Skiing.
滑雪
Shoop,shoop,shoop....
咻,咻,咻….
Shoop.
咻
-Eww. -What?
-噢! -什么?
Ugly Naked Guy's taking his turkey out of the oven.
丑陋裸男正从烤炉中取出他的火鸡
-Who cares? -He just sat in gravy.
-谁在乎啊? -他刚刚坐到肉汤里了
Oh,my God! He's not alone.
噢,我的天.丑陋裸男不是一个人
Ugly Naked Guy is having Thanksgiving dinner with Ugly Naked Gal.
他正和一个丑陋裸女共进感恩节晚餐
I gotta see this!
我得看看
All right,Ugly Naked Guy!
丑陋裸男真爽!
Ugly naked dancing!
裸舞开场了!
It's nice that he has someone.
有人陪真好
Shall I carve?
可以切了吗?
-By all means. -All right.
-怎样都行 -当然可以
Who wants light cheese, and who wants dark cheese?
谁想要浅色起司,谁想要深色起司?
I don't even want to know about the dark cheese.
我一点也不想知道深色起司是怎么来的
-Does anybody wanna split this? -I will.
-有人想要和我分这块吗? -噢,我要
-You guys have to make a wish. -Make a wish?
你们必须先许个愿望. -许愿?
Come on,you know,Thanksgiving.
来吧,这是感.恩.节!
You got the bigger half! What did you wish for?
噢!你得到大半了.你许的什么愿?
The bigger half.
得到大半
All right,I'd like to propose a toast.
我敬各位一杯
A little toast here. Ding,ding!
来一杯,ding ding
This isn't the Thanksgiving you planned...
我知道这不是你们本来计划的感恩节
...but for me, this has been really great.
但是对我来说,这样也挺棒的
I think because it didn't involve divorce or projectile vomiting.
我想,这是因为它没和离婚或者呕吐搭界
If you'd gone to Vail or if you had been with your family...
如果你去了韦尔,如果你没离婚
...or if you didn't have syphilis and stuff...
你没有……“梅毒”那些玩意
...we wouldn't be together.
我们就不能一起过
I guess what l' m trying to say is that...
所以我想说的就是:
... I' m very thankful that all of your Thanksgivings sucked.
谢天谢地你们的感恩节计划都砸了
-That's so sweet! -Thank you.
-真是感人! -谢谢
-Here's to a lousy Christmas! -And a crappy New Year!
-祝你有个糟糕的圣诞节. -还有一个失败的新年
-Hear,hear! -Hear,hear!
-干! -干!
小便失禁!
停止家庭暴力 !
有痔疮吗?
三次“东尼奖”获得者